A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1986-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1986-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.891
This collection consists of 23,700 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1989 September 4.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1986-1987; seldom used permanent files, 1970-1987; development solicitations, 1981-1987; and, committee and task force files, 1972-1988.
Permanent records concern: development solicitations; Constitution Bicentennial; condolences; and, Visitors-Audit Committee.
Organization
Series I: General Files, 1986-1987 Boxes 1-44
Series II: Seldom-Used Permanent Files, 1970-1987 Boxes 44-49
Series III: Development Solicitation Files, 1981-1987 Boxes 50-59
Series IV: Committees and Task Forces Files, 1972-1988 Boxes 60-64
Contents List
- Series I: General Files
  - "A" Miscellaneous (5 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Administration--General 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Computing Services 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Admissions--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Law 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Admissions--Medical (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Afro-American Affairs--General 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Afro-American Affairs--Woodson Institute 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Association--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Alumni--Letters 1986 Jul 24 (Box 2)
  - Alumni--Letters 1985 Nov (Box 3)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association (2 folders) 1986 Jul-1987 Jan (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association (1 of 3) 1987 Feb-Jun (Box 3)
  - American Bar Association (2-3 of 3) 1987 Feb-Jun (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - American Frontier Culture Foundation--General 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Anthropology 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions (2 of 3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions (3 of 3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Architecture 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Art--General 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Asian Studies 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Associated Western Universities 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Colleges (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Association of American Universities (3 folders) 1986 Jan- 1987 Jun (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities--Fall Meetings 1986 Oct (Box 6)
  - Association of Governing Boards 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Association of Research Libraries 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Astronomy 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Athletics--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--ACC 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--CFA 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Athletics--NCAA (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General (State) 1986-1987 (Box 7)
  - Auditor--Internal (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (1of 6) 1986-1987 (Box 8)
  - "B" Miscellaneous (2-6 of 6) 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Biology--General 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Business and Finance--Executive Planning Group 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (1-5 of 11) 1986-1987 (Box 10)
  - "C" Miscellaneous (6-11 of 11) 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Carnegie Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Center for Innovative Technology II (4 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 12)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Charlottesville, City of 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Charlottesville--Planning and Coordination Council 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Chemistry 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - China 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Civil Rights 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Classics 1986-1987 (Box 13)
  - Clinch Valley College--General (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - College Board 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Commerce 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Comptroller (State) 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Congress 1986-1987 (Box 14)
  - Consortia--Tidewater 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Consortia--Western 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Council of Presidents 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Council on Library Resources 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Council on Postsecondary Accreditation (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Council on Postsecondary Accredited--Task Force on Education Quality 1987 (Box 16)
  - COPA Self-Study Advisory Panel Hearings 1986 Jul (Box 16)
  - "D" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business Administration 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Darden School--Darden Business Sponsors 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Dean's Meetings 1986-1987 (Box 16)
  - Development--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Drama 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - "E" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - Education 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Educational Testing Service 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Applied Sciences: Engineering Development Committee 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Building (State) 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - English 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Enrollment--General 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Environmental Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - Equal Opportunity Office--General 1986-1987 (Box 18)
  - "F" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Faculty--General 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Faculty Letter (4 folders) 1986 Sep-1987 May (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - Food Services 1986-1987 (Box 19)
  - French 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - "G" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 20)
  - General Assembly (3 folders) 1987 Jan-Jun (Box 20)
  - General Assembly (2 folders) 1986 Jul-Dec (Box 21)
  - General Services 1986-1987 (Box 21)
  - German 1986-1987 (Box 21)
  - Gifts and Grants (1-2 of 5) 1986-1987 (Box 21)
  - Gifts and Grants (3-5 of 5) 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Governmental Relations 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Governor's Office--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Administration 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Commerce and Resources 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Education 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Finance 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Human Resources 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office--Washington Liaison Office 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Governor--Virginia/Israel Commission (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - "H" Miscellaneous (4 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Higher Education of 1965--Title IV 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - History 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Honor System 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - Housing 1986-1987 (Box 24)
  - "I" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Informative Technology--State 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Institute of Government 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Institutional Planning and Studies 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - "J" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation--General 1986-1987 (Box 25)
  - Johnson Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Johnson Foundation--Wingspread Journal 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - "L" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 26)
  - Law--General (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - Lawn Policy Use (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - Lawn Society--Advisory Group 1987 (Box 27)
  - Legal Adviser's Office--General 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - Library--General 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - "M" Miscellaneous (6 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 28)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development (MASD) 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Marine Science 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Mariner's Museum (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Materials Management (Purchasing) 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Medical Center--General 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1986-1987 (Box 29)
  - Medical Center--Council of Trustees 1987 (Box 29)
  - Medical Hospital--General 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Medical Hospital--Personnel 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Medical School--General 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Medical School--Personnel 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Medical Nursing--General 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Medical Nursing--Personnel 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - Music 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - "N" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 30)
  - NASULGC--General (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - NASULGC--Green Circulars 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - National Science Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - O'Neil, Robert M.--General 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - O'Neil--Class 1986-1987 (Box 31)
  - Online Computer Library Center (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - "P" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - Parking and Transportation-General 1986-1987 (Box 32)
  - Personnel--General 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Personnel and Training (State) 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Physical Plant 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Physics 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Planning--Miscellaneous (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Planning--Project Status Reports (Construction report) 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget Capital Outlay 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget State 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Planning and Budget (UVA) 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Poynter Institute 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Promotions 1986-1987 (Box 33)
  - Provost 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - Provost--Associate for Research 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - Psychology 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - "R" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - Real Estate, Risk Management and Safety 1986-1987 (Box 34)
  - Recommendations A-Z (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - Registrar 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - Religious Studies 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--General 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Army 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - ROTC--Navy 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (1-3 of 7) 1986-1987 (Box 35)
  - "S" Miscellaneous (4-7 of 7) 1986-1987 (Box 36)
  - Senate (University) (1 of 2) 1986-1987 (Box 36)
  - Senate (University) (2 of 2) 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Small Business Development Center--Incubator 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Small Business Development Center--Working Group 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Sociology 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - South Regional Education Board--General 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - South Regional Education Board--Publications 1985-1986 (Box 37)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Southern Association of Landgrant Colleges and State Universities 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Spanish, Italian and Portuguese 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - Sponsored Programs 1986-1987 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education--General (5 folders) 1986 Jul-1987 Jun (Box 38)
  - State Council of Higher Education--Council Notes 1986-1987 (Box 38)
  - State Council of Higher Education--"On Line" 1986-1987 (Box 38)
  - State Department of Education 1986-1987 (Box 39)
  - Student Affairs--General (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 39)
  - Student Affairs--Letter to Parents of New Students 1986-1987 (Box 39)
  - Student Affairs--Fraternities 1986-1987 (Box 39)
  - Student Council--General 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - Summer Session 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - "T" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1986-1987 (Box 40)
  - Travel Invoices (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - Treasurer 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - "U" Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - United States Savings Bond 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - United Way 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - Universities Research Association 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - University Guides 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - University Journal 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - University Police 1986-1987 (Box 41)
  - University Press of Virginia 1986-1987 (Box 42)
  - University Relations 1986-1987 (Box 42)
  - University Union 1986-1987 (Box 42)
  - "V" Miscellaneous (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 42)
  - Vice Presidents' Meetings (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - Virginia Judicial System Commission 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (1-2 of 4) 1986-1987 (Box 43)
  - "W" Miscellaneous (3-4 of 4) 1986-1987 (Box 44)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous 1986-1987 (Box 44)
- Series II: Seldom-Used Permanent Files
  - Administrative Seminar (2 folders) 1986 Aug 28 (Box 44)
  - Admissions--Entering Student Profiles 1970-1986 (Box 44)
  - Athletics--Schultz, Richard D. 1981-1989 (Box 45)
  - Auxiliary Services Foundation 1984 (Box 45)
  - Clinch Valley College--Moomaw 1986-1987 (Box 45)
  - Condolences "A-P" (3 folders) 1980-1987 (Box 45)
  - Condolences "Q-Z" 1980-1987 (Box 46)
  - Constitutional Bicentennial II (Perm) (3 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 46)
  - Darden, Colgate II (Perm) 1980-1987 (Box 47)
  - Development--McLeod, Shelton 1981-1986 (Box 47)
  - Development--Owen, John J. 1976-1982 (Box 47)
  - Education--Ward, Virgil 1983-1986 (Box 47)
  - Equal Opportunity--A.A. (Perm)--Wilson, Hope W. 1986-1987 (Box 47)
  - Inauguration Committee--O'Neil (2 folders) 1985 (Box 47)
  - Lawn Society 1986 Nov (Box 48)
  - Legal Adviser (Perm)--Information Systems 1984 (Box 48)
  - Visitors--Audit Committee (3 folders) 1981-1987 (Box 48)
  - Visitors--Presidential Working Papers 1979 (Box 48)
  - Visitors--Special Committee--Search for Chancellor of Clinch Valley College 1984-1985 (Box 49)
  - Visitors--Special Committee--Fraternity/Sorority Housing (2 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 49)
  - Visitors--Special Committee--Honor System 1983-1985 (Box 49)
  - Visitors--Special Committee--Real Estate 1985-1986 (Box 49)
- Series III: Development Solicitations
  - "A" 1985-1987 (Box 50)
  - "ATandT" (2 folders) 1982-1986 (Box 50)
  - "Ba-Bn" 1985-1987 (Box 50)
  - "Bo-Bz" (1 of 2) 1985-1987 (Box 50)
  - "Bo-Bz" (2 of 3) 1985-1987 (Box 51)
  - "C" (2 folders) 1983-1987 (Box 51)
  - "Da-Dr" 1984-1987 (Box 51)
  - "Ds-Fe" 1985-1987 (Box 52)
  - DuPont de Nemours and Co. 1982-1987 (Box 52)
  - DuPont (Jessie Ball) 1981-1987 (Box 52)
  - Exxon Education Foundation 1981-1987 (Box 52)
  - "Ff-Fz" (2 folders) 1983-1987 (Box 52)
  - Figgie, Harry E. Jr. 1982-1987 (Box 53)
  - Fitzgerald Foundation 1982-1987 (Box 53)
  - "Ga-Gz" (2 folders) 1984-1986 (Box 53)
  - General Electric 1984-1987 (Box 53)
  - "H" (1 of 2) 1981-1987 (Box 53)
  - "H" (2 of 2) 1981-1987 (Box 54)
  - Harrison (2 folders) 1982-1987 (Box 54)
  - "I-Ke" (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 54)
  - IBM (2 folders) 1982-1986 (Box 55)
  - Japan (1-2 of 3) 1982-1987 (Box 55)
  - Japan (3 of 3) 1982-1987 (Box 56)
  - Japan II 1985-1987 (Box 56)
  - Jones Foundation (W. Alton) 1979-1987 (Box 56)
  - "Kf-Kz" 1982-1987 (Box 56)
  - "L" 1985-1987 (Box 56)
  - "Ma-Mc" (1 of 3) 1985-1987 (Box 56)
  - "Ma-Mc" (2-3 of 3) 1985-1987 (Box 57)
  - "Md-Mz" (2 folders) 1983-1987 (Box 57)
  - "N-O" (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 57)
  - "P" (2 folders) 1981-1987 (Box 58)
  - "Q-Sg" (2 folders) 1985-1987 (Box 58)
  - "Sh-Sz" (1 of 2) 1985-1987 (Box 58)
  - "Sh-Sz" (2 of 2) 1985-1987 (Box 59)
  - "T-Wg" (2 folders) 1985-1987 (Box 59)
  - "Wh-Z" 1985-1987 (Box 59)
- Series IV: Committees and Task Forces
  - University Committees 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee--General 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Afro-American Affairs Advisory 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Arboretum and Landscape 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Architectural Advisory (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Athletic Advisory Council 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Bayly Museum 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Calendar 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Chapel 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Chemical and Biological Hazards Safety 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Chemical and Biological Safety--Subcommittee DNA 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Commencement and Convocations 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Community Colleges 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Computing and Communications 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Development Policy 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Energy Conservation 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Equal Opportunity 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Faculty Benefits 1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Financial Aid 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Fraternities and Sororities 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Fulbright Grants 1986-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee --Future of the University (Permanent) 1972-1987 (Box 60)
  - Administrative Committee--Graphics 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Gwathmey Award 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Housing 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--International Students 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Lectures--Page, Barbours, and Richard 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Libraries 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Library and Science Engineering Library-Subcommittee (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Master Planning Council 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Names 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Proxy Advisory 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Radiation Safety 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Radiation Safety--Subcommittee: Radioactive Drug Research 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Registration 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Research Policy Advisory (empty) n.d. (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Residential Life 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Rhodes Scholarship 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--ROTC 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Scheduling 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Scholarships, Grants-in-aid, Employment and Loans (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Security and General Safety 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Student Activities 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Student Health 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Summer Grants 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Summer Sessions 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Thomas Jefferson Award 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Traffic and Parking 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Traffic Appeals 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Truman Scholarships 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Undergraduate Admissions 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--University Committee on Judicial Policy 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--University Committee on Students (empty) 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--University Press of Virginia 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--University Research Policy Advisory 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--University Union and Student Activities Buildings 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Virginia Quarterly Review 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Administrative Committee--Virginia Status of Students 1986-1987 (Box 62)
  - Special Committee--Asbestos Removal 1984-1986 (Box 62)
  - Task Force--Classified Research (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 62)
  - Task Force--Committee to Recommend Policies for Use of Lawn 1986-1988 (Box 62)
  - Task Force--Committee to Recommend Policies for Use of Rotunda 1986 (Box 62)
  - Task Force--Faculty Handbook II (2 folders) 1987-1988 (Box 62)
  - Task Force--Faculty Handbook I (2 folders) 1986 (Box 63)
  - Task Force--Working Group on General Faculty 1986-1987 (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of Afro-American Affairs 1986 (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Athletic Director Search 1987 (Box 63)
  - Single, Douglas n.d. (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of Continuing Education 1986-1987 (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Dean of Law School 1986-1988 (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Director of University Press 1987-1988 (Box 63)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for Position of Equal Opportunity/A.A. Officer (2 folders) 1985-1987 (Box 64)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for VP for Health Affairs (Part I) (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 64)
  - Ad Hoc Committee--Search for VP for Health Affairs (Part II) (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 64)